Amanda Sealshaw. Let's get into it. Today's goes to Tamiya Brevard Rodriguez. She had a plan
called Operation Dissertation Before Baby. So she was determined to finish her dissertation
before her baby's due date. But baby, the baby had other plans. Literally while she was preparing,
her water broke. Her wife, being the baller that she is, pulls up, skirt, skirt, in the
off, they zoomed to the hospital. But the baby was like, nah, I'm ready now. And she delivered
her own baby in the passenger seat of her wife's ride. Here's where the big up happens. They get
to the hospital and then she gave her presentation. She literally defended her PhD while she was in the
hospital post birth. Don't give black women a curveball. We'll make it clap. Okay. Today's
lockdown. Okay. Picture this. You're casually strolling down the aisle of a Southwest flight,
ready to stash your carry on when suddenly you do a double take. There's a woman lounging inside the
overhead luggage compartment. What? Yeah. Like it's a bunk bed. I'm really curious to know where this was
because if it was New York, not even surprised. I wouldn't be surprised if people still put their
bag in the compartment with her. Like Shorty, move your legs, move your legs. She's up there like,
I'm holding this down from my bag. It's coming. It's coming. You know how people be standing
in the space for a parking lot? Right.